Whether your computers ready or not,
there are only 318 days till the year 2000.
A group of corporations concerned
about the problems
related to the Y2K computer bug
have convened...
No. Dont cry.
Dont cry. Hey.
Everythings gonna be okay.
Hi. Everythings gonna be okay, pal.
Come here, come here. Yeah.
Thats a good boy. Okay, dont cry.
She cant hurt you anymore.
Its over. Come here.
No ones gonna hurt you ever again.
My name is Louis Hicks.
Im an investigative reporter.
I cover stories of killers and criminals.
Their lives are dark, without hope.
I try not to let it affect me, but its hard.
-Hey! Gordo! Two shots.
-No!
-Yes, yes.
-No, no, no, no.
-I got to work in an hour.
-Just one, just one.
-No, no.
-One shot, old-school.
-One. One shot.
-There it is.
-To Louis.
-Yeah.
All right, now you do something for me.
Let me buy you breakfast.
Too late. I already ate.
Breakfast of champions.
Hows work? Any compelling
real-life stories I should know about?
Not today.
Well...
Hows work for you, huh?
You working on the book?
Always. Always working, Gordo.